

Eduardo Alexandre L opes Janeiro Pires

ID: 14825856

Date of birth: 17/12/1996

Place of birth: Barreiro, Portugal

Nationality: Portuguese

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Rua de Timor N°11 2°D2830-065 Barreiro, Portugal(Home)

eduardoalexandre.pires96@gm ail.com

(+351) 919112513

(+351) 919112513 **(WhatsApp)**



ABOUT ME

I am an adaptable and dedicated professional currently transitioning into the world of software development. My career path has been diverse—from working in elevator maintenance to hospitality and logistics—giving me a strong work ethic, resilience, and people skills. I have always balanced my professional life with my passion for teaching, having been a combat sports coach since the age of 18.

I am fluent in Portuguese and English, with working knowledge of French and Spanish, and I am currently learning Japanese. I enjoy learning new things, solving problems, and always strive for excellence in everything I do. In my free time, I love being around animals, staying active through training, and exploring new ideas and skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ascensurel Lda. Barreiro, Portugal

lift technician 09/2015 – 03/2017

Bitz & Savoye SA Sion, Switzerland

locksmith

03/2017 - 08/2017

Grupnor Elevadores Porto, Portugal

lift technician

08/2017 - 05/2018

Peixe e Companhia Costa da Caparica, Portugal

waiter/waitress

06/2018 - 09/2018

Nogueira's Lisboa, Portugal

waiter/waitress

10/2018 - 05/2019

Selplus Lisboa, Portugal

Field Operations Coordinator

06/2019 - 12/2019

Hotel Paradise Ftan, Switzerland

hotel concierge

05/2020 - 04/2022

Educoach e AT Brilhantes Barreiro, Portugal

Physical Activities Teacher

09/2022 - 06/2024

Galeria Lisboa, Portugal

Telemarketing Operator

08/2023 - 08/2024

CTT Lisboa, Portugal

Contract Management 09/2024 – Current

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Barreiro, Portugal

Social-Economic Sciences Escola Secundária de Santo André

Level in EQF EQF level 4

Box Instrutor

CAP or CCP

12/2024 - CURRENT Palmela, Portugal

Information Technology (IT) System Specialist ATEC

Level in EQF EQF level 5

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Portuguese

Other language(s):

English

Listening C2

Spoken production C2

Reading C2

Spoken interaction C2

Writing C2

French

Listening B1

Spoken production B1

Reading B1

Spoken interaction B1

Writing B1

Spanish

Listening B1

Spoken production B1

Reading B1

Spoken interaction B1

Writing B1

Japanese

Listening A1

Spoken production A1

Reading A1

Spoken interaction A1

Writing A1

DRIVING LICENCE



Driving Licence: A1
Driving Licence: B